So this doesn't end here, it actually starts here.
We also have a text tab over here in the Microsoft Design Editor,
and what we can do over here is pretty obvious.
So we can add a text and let's wait until the rest is loaded.
So we can see what else is doable over here.
So as you see, some of them are being loaded.
So these are already prepared kind of effects and text effects that you can apply and you can adjust.
So by clicking on this start for example, the color and the phone family and the phone size and all of that will be set to a default, you know?
And these defaults are being generated over here as you see.
So you can use these presets, text effects.
But I click on add text so I don't want any of these presets.
And as you see a text box is added over here.
So as you see, we still have text styles open over here and we can choose among them in order to set a certain phone family, phone style, you know, or phone color, you know, kind of effects, styles, shadows, etc.
So all of these are available.
But I want to go ahead with this very pure text that I have over here.
So I add something, I say the take of, hold on, the take of college, for example.
And as you see, I can select, I can come here and change the phone family.
So if I click over here, as you see, I can change it to let's say elephant pro, for example.
Yes, so this is doable as you see, I can change the phone size.
So I increase it, I can set it to bold, italic, underline, you know, strike all of these text formatting options, as well as text alignments and spacing and vertical alignment, as well as effects.
So in effects, I can add shadows to my text.
I can add background to my text, I can add outlines and I can arach or wave my text, all of these effects are available as well.
And we also have transparency, position and copy stars.
So I come here and I position my cursor in a way that the like cursor pointer changes to this moving option.
And then I can click and drag and my text will be moved to wherever that I want.